[{"answer": "Well, I justified in the name of conservation.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "How do you justify what you have done?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Why not just give it to them?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "I accept as a starting place -- point in Namibia, that there are surplus of them and they are about to be taken off of the endangered species list, Piers.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Do you accept that as a starting point?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "I intend to take trophy photos of the animal in a respectful manner so I can remember it, so I can give it to the Namibian government -- to the Namibian people, and honor the animal as what it is.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Do you intend to do that?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "It hasn't made me think twice but, Piers, to be honest 100 percent, I had no idea that it would be this visceral.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Has it made you -- has their reaction, however, well-reasoned or unreasoned -- has the venom of the reaction and the amount of the reaction made you think twice about going through with this?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Murder?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Well, some things ...", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "What do you say when you're eating a steak, Piers?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Well, of course the secretary of state and ultimately the President of United States, and members of the State Department, and others who were involved in this really unusual set of circumstances that not only led to the deaths of these four brave Americans but the events afterwards which would basically a cover up.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Who is to blame?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's important to point out that he had asked for additional assistance.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "And obviously, you know, you don't want to speak ill of a man who was killed in such appalling circumstances, but is it fair to also say that he as the Ambassador should have done more to react to direct warnings that he was given on numerous occasions?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Of course, not.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do you not accept that?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, in the Bridgegate as it turned out, may not have directly cost lives but it couldn't, I mean, we couldn't have been in the position ...", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "I think that's a huge difference, don't you?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "I'm good Piers.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Mr. Mayor, how are you?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, there's only one big pitfall going ahead and that is, if his telling the truth, I believe that he is.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "How is he doing in this scandal, do you think, and what are the big pitfalls going ahead?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's another very critical difference.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Why are Republicans supportive of Chris Christie whereas reserving the right to hammer Hillary Clinton for what many would argue is the same position politically?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I have, yes.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Have you spoken to him at all since this crisis unfold?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "That's between him and me.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What did you say to him?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "The NRA is pretty strong and I think they can handle it.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Well, I'm better than I deserved, Piers.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I would share that view actually about myself.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Well, let's start with I'm not sure they know.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "It's like a lot of other things.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "But how do you control it financially?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Well, he's obviously very bright and can understand a lot of things.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "You obviously agree with that?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "He taught us how to communicate and how to budget.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "What was it that Dave told you that really helped you do this?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Well, the shorter answer would be what we were doing right as a couple at that time.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "What was it you were doing wrong, Ashley, as a couple that Dave corrected in your heads, enabled you to start really saving money?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Well, I think Ashley touched on it.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "When you looked at Chad and Ashley's story, what were the key issues that you felt needed to be very quickly remedied?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Well, we hear all the time that debit cards are not as safe as credit cards.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "Dave?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "That would be a myth.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Myth or truth?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Well, that will be a myth unless you're going to be crazy or something.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Myth or truth?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "It's so much less stressful.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "But what is the single best thing about being debt-free, having spent so many years riddled with debt as a couple what would you say?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "And to do what we're doing right now.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Ashley what would you say?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Oh man, he's our hero.", "docId": "140116pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "What would you both say to Dave Ramsey given he's been instrumental in wiping out this debt?", "qSentId": 692}]